THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
他们来啦
Here they are!
他在干... 他在干什么呢
What's he do... What's he doing?
拜托 没事的
Come on, it'll be fine.
车可以通过的
It'll fit!
恐怕他不会开过来的
I'm afraid he's not gonna drive through.
-他说车过不来  -但明显是能过的
- He says it won't fit. - Well, clearly it'll fit.
他以为他是谁 汽车人吗[变形金刚]
What is he, vehicle dysmorphic?
桥的承重是三吨半
The bridge has a three-and-a-half ton weight limit,
而且他还担心擦到后视镜
and he's worried about his mirrors.
到底是哪个原因 夏洛特
Well, which is it, Charlotte?
东拉西扯的
The story keeps changing.
下车吧
Come on down!
这跟我设想的迎宾不太一样
This is not my intended welcome.
我们会... 我们会解决好的 汤姆
We will... We will sort it, Tom.
-早上好  -幸会
- Morning! - Hey, good to see ya.
我们可以准备些四轮马车...
We can just get buggies and...
四轮马车 那他妈要花多久
Buggies? How the fuck long will that take?
我们只要召集一些马车然后...
We just need to round up the buggies and...
我在酒店行业工作 夏洛特 我知道什么是胡扯
I work in hospitality, Charlotte, so I can smell bullshit.
-妈妈  -宝贝
- Mom! - Honey!
来啦 爸爸
Hey, Daddy!
来了 小汤 见到你真高兴
Hey, Tommy, it's great to see ya.
等了好几个小时吗
Couple of hours?!
坐在那里挺不错的
It was wonderful just sitting there.
我们喜欢看飞机
We liked watching the planes.
你爸爸觉得他好像看到了
Your father thought he might have seen
一个U2乐队的成员[爱尔兰摇滚乐队]
the man from U2.
-好吧  -还有阿瑟·拉伐[经济学家]
- OK. - And Arthur Laffer,
拉伐曲线的那个拉伐 他们都会来吗
of the Laffer Curve? Are they coming?
好吧 可能吧 来的都是些摇滚天王和经济学家
Well, could be. It's mostly rock gods and economists.
苍蝇伙计来啦
Hey, hey, it's the Fly Guys!
-很高兴见到你们  -你做到了 兄弟
- Good to see you! - You made it, man!
小汤 你妈有点渴了
Tommy, your mother's a little thirsty.
-妈咪 你渴了吗  -有一点
- Mommy, you thirsty? - A little thirsty.
我不想麻烦你 汤姆 是我的不对
I don't want to be a trouble, Tom. It was my fault.
拿上包 然后我们去...
Grab a bag, and then we'll go...
我会跟着你们的
I'll follow you up.
你现在高兴了吧 夏洛特
I hope you're happy now, Charlotte,
因为我妈渴得要死
'cause my mother is dying of thirst.
我又拎起了包
And I've just picked up a bag.
在我的婚礼前夕 我居然拎着行李箱
I'm carrying a case on my wedding eve.
翻译: 奶啾
翻译: 负能量小天使
翻译: Ciaran
翻译: 一个吃外卖度日的大佬
翻译: Francis
翻译: 走油肉
翻译: 海顿
翻译: 咩咩恩
时间轴: Heiforn
时间轴: 阿布
特效: 小布
后期&压制: Jason肖
校对:渡渡
校对：宇宙万宝路
继     承
第 一 季  第９集
"婚礼前夕"
监制: 宇宙万宝路
伦敦希思罗国际机场
好了 我该走了
All right. I gotta go.
但我们婚礼上见 好吗
But I'll see you there, OK?
我改了去大使馆的时间
I managed to change the time for the embassy,
另外...
and...
-不好意思 一切还好吗  -没事
- Sorry. Are we OK? - Yeah.
吉尔 如果你很忙的话
Gil, you don't have to come to the wedding
没必要来参加婚礼 那...
if you're too busy. That's...
我们刚才一直在监视媒体
We've just been doing the media monitoring.
操他妈的 我他妈要把他杀了
Motherfuckers. I'll fucking kill him.
大卸八块
I'll take them to pieces!
他没睡觉
He's not sleeping.
是个不知名的人 惹怒了他
It's what's-his-name. Got under his skin.
大众脸
Screwdriver-face.
那段啊...
The bit...
他暗示吉尔谋杀了自己妻子的段子
The bit where he implied he murdered his wife.
狂躁的参议员是否是妻子走向崩溃边缘的推手
没错 不知怎么的这让主播很"困扰"
Yeah, for some reason that's somewhat irked him.
狂躁的参议员是否是妻子走向崩溃边缘的推手
吉尔 你不用关注这个 我们可以解决的
Gil, you don't need to focus on this. We can hit it.
我懂 我专注着呢
I know. I'm focused.
我正在细读这个简报 寻求重要事实
I'm X-raying this briefing for salient facts.
我也不想在这件事上大做文章
I mean, I don't want to make a big thing out of this,
但是有没有可能你爸
but is it possible your father
是这个世界上穷凶极恶之人呢
is the worst human being who ever lived?
我... 我觉得那不...
I... I don't think that's...
他不出席婚礼真的是为了
Is it true he's not coming to the wedding,
为了... 干嘛 出口恶气吗
out of... what, spite?
这很复杂
Well, it's complicated.
我要拿下他
I want to take him out.
我要摧毁泛美网络科技公司
I want to destroy ATN.
我觉得这不太明智
I'm not sure that's wise.
那如果我说这很明智
And if I said it was wise,
你还有异议吗
would you have a problem with that?
没有
No.
到最后 吉尔 我会如你所愿做任何事
In the end, Gil, I'll do whatever you want.
西沃恩 听着 如果你能给我点猛料
Siobhan, look. If there's something,
哪怕一点 都给我吧
anything, you can get me,
我他妈正在参与一场刀站
I'm in a fuckin' knife fight here,
却拿着一根用美国干酪做的人造阳具
I'm holding a dildo made out of American cheese.
真的要这么做 是吗
So this is really gonna happen, yeah?
你知道我不想中国工商银行成为财团的一部分 对吧
You know I don't want ICBC as part of the syndicate, right?
75到150个基点
75 to 150 basis points,
和0.2%的承诺费
and point two percent commitment fee.
然后 然后 对的
Then, then, yeah. Fuck yeah.
-我觉得可以  -真他妈的
- I feel good. - Holy shit.
没了他们咱们就能开始了 我晚点打给你
Without them we're good to go. Let me call you back.
你妹妹听说过科莫湖吗
Has your sister ever heard of Lake Como?
科莫湖: 位于意大利北部阿尔卑斯山区
她听说过威尼斯 圣巴特岛 马尔代夫吗
Has she ever heard of Venice, St. Barts, the Maldives?
圣巴特岛: 位于加勒比海上的法属西印度群岛小岛屿
她听说过这些地方吗 她至少知道吧
Has she heard of these locations? She must be aware of them.
我接到电话了 你呢
I got the call. You get the call?
我也接到这个狗日的电话了
I got the fuckin' call.
我们要进去吗 来吧
Shall we go inside? Come on.
什么 在这里吗
What? In here?
兄弟 我们正在策划一起针对世界上
Brother, we are putting together a hostile takeover
最大的媒体企业之一的
of one of the largest media corporations
恶意收购
in the world.
我觉得我们可以开一瓶无年份香槟
I think we can brave some non-vintage champagne.
能给我们弄点香槟吗
Can we get some champagne?
来一瓶 谢谢
A bottle, please? Thank you.
怎么样 等个大概十天
What are we talkin'? Like ten days?
然后我们杀入其中吗
Then we go in for the kill?
-没错  -无法保持封锁状态
- Yeah. - Can't keep it on lockdown
超过十天 是吗
for more than about ten days, right?
-对 就是这样  -约翰
- Yeah, that's about it. - John?
-约翰 约翰  -那么 就像...
- John? John! - So, like...
你找到什么香槟了没
Have you got any that champagne?
...19号开始熊抱吗
...the 19th for the bear hug?
狗熊式拥抱: 具有威胁性质的高溢价收购邀约
-是的 好 还有一件小事  -好的
- Yeah. Good. One little thing. - Good.
那些加拿大人 他们好像对一些细节有点不满
The Canadians, there seems to be a little static on some details.
-比如说  -比如... 让你做总裁
- Like what? - Like... you as CEO.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
放松 好吗
Relax. OK?
这件事没你是不可能的
This doesn't happen without you.
合作投资人之间经常出这种幺蛾子
It's normal co-investor bullshit.
弗兰克了解这些人 你想让我...
Frank knows those guys. You want me to...
我会处理好的 伙计
I'll handle it, dude.
别走漏消息 拜托 别告诉弗兰克 别告诉任何人
No leaks. Please. Not to Frank, not to anyone.
你为什么神经兮兮的 小肯
Why are you so jumpy about this, Ken?
为什么神经兮兮
Why am I jumpy?
还不是因为该死的罗曼 小西和康纳
About fucking Rome, fuckin' Shiv and Connor,
大概是把老爸剩下的脑水全刮干净了
probably blowing what's left of my dad's fuckin' brain?
因为要永远让公司脱离家族掌控
About taking the company out of family control, forever?
我不知道 斯图伊 那为什么让我神经兮兮的
I don't know, Stewy. Why would that make me jumpy?
听着 我他妈的不在乎
Look, I don't give a fuck.
但我的意思是 你想让我去问问吗
But, I mean, do you want me to ask?
我就是想看看她会不会来求我
I'm just curious to see if she's gonna come begging.
-我真的可以问一句的  -我不想问
- Because I can ask.  - I don't want to ask.
如果她想问 没人不让她问
If she wants to ask, she can ask.
因为我已经看到她了
'Cause I can physically see her.
格丽 我不想问
Gerri, I don't want to ask.
好吧
Ok.
她爬到我脚边跪求原谅
She comes crawling,
没准我会考虑一下
then I'll think it over.
-好吧 好 我懂了  -谁在那儿
- Fine. OK, I get it.  - Who's there?
-就...  -你见到卡洛琳了吗
- Um...  - Have you seen Caroline?
她还和那个短下巴的嬉皮蠢蛋在一起吗
Is she still with that chinless hippie prick?
我还以为会错过彩排呢
I thought we might miss the rehearsal.
不需要彩排 我们会秒杀全场的
We don't need to rehearse. We're gonna kill it.
你有没有再想过你爸的事
Did you think again about your dad
我们是不是也该重新考虑...
and whether we want to reconsider...
-去他妈的  -没错 没错
- Fuck him.  - Right, right.
你有没有再考虑过 我们是要自称"威姆士丹夫妇"
And did you think again about whether we want to go Wambsgans
或"罗伊-威姆士丹夫妇" 再或者 像我之前说的
or Roy-Wambsgans or, as I said,
我很愿意颠覆传统
I'd be willing to just drop traditional
改成"汤姆·罗伊"也行 真的 就我而言 如果...
and go Tom Roy, in fact, for myself, if...
那个 我想问你点事
Hey, I wanted to ask you something.
你说
Uh-huh?
我想知道在邮轮上发生的坏事
I could do with knowing about the bad thing in Cruises.
就是让你睡不着的那件事
You know, the thing that meant you couldn't sleep?
这样啊
Uh-huh.
-不想说吗  -我...
- No?  - I...
不是 我没有...
No, I don't...
不 我只是觉得 行
No, I just think, yeah,
我在想 你知道的 教会和国家...
I just think, you know, church and state and...
还有AC/DC[澳大利亚摇滚乐队]...
and AC/DC and...
乌木与象牙 这些都是水火不容的
ebony and ivory and never the twain shall meet.
好吧 但你一直想将这些公诸于世
Yeah, right, but you always wanted to make it public.
-不是吗  -是的 没错
- Didn't you?  - Yes. Yeah.
-我真心想说出来  -就是说啊
- In my bones, I did.  - Exactly.
但我后来毁了所有证据 所以...
But I did then destroy all the evidence, so...
我猜... 如果是件坏事
I guess... you know, if it's bad,
你置之不理得越久
the longer you leave it,
真相大白时情况就越糟糕
the worse it'll be when it comes out.
是的 除非让它石沉大海 懂吗
Yes, unless it never comes out. You know?
我打赌事情根本没有那么糟
I bet it's not even that bad.
其实真挺糟的
Uh, it is quite bad.
特别糟糕
It's quite bad.
-操 我们到了  -看吧 亲爱的
- Oh, fuck, here we go.  - Look, honey.
这就是梦想实现的地方
This is where it's happening.
-你好啊  -你好
- Oh, hey.  - Hey.
-真激动  -你好
- It's exciting!  - Hey.
你跟"西部恶婊"说过话了吗
You spoken to the Wicked Bitch of the West yet?
我刚到这儿 小西
I just got here, Shiv.
会耽误很久吗
Is this gonna take long?
进去吧
Shall we?
-备马出征 士兵们  -得了吧
- Saddle up, soldier.  - Oh, come on.
她不可能这么恐怖
She can't be that bad.
行吧 不要直视她的眼睛就行
Yeah, just don't look at her directly.
你好 你们好哇
Hello! Hello, hello!
-你好  -你可算来了
- Hi.  - Here you are.
我知道你肯定会来的
I knew you'd arrive eventually.
汤姆 记得小塔吗
Tom. Remember Tabs?
-这是我母亲  -你好
- My mom.  - Hello!
-汤姆  -你好
- Tom.  - Hi.
天呐 瞧瞧你
Gosh, look at you.
看起来很合理
You're very plausible.
谢谢
Thank you.
没错
Exactly.
-你好 妈妈  -你好 肯德尔
- Hi, Mom.  - Hi, Kendall.
这是塔比莎 你们见过吗
Tabitha, have you guys met?
-你们都见过...  -哥们
- Have you all...  - Bro.
汪 汪 汪
Ruff ruff! Ruff!
那么 我们开始扮快乐一家子吧
So, shall we go and play happy families?
没问题 好极了
Yes. Great.
没错
Mm-hmm.
人选得不错
Well done on Tom.
是吗 谢谢你
Oh, yeah. Thank you.
再跟我说一遍 你为什么跟他结婚
Tell me again why you're marrying him.
-妈妈 别这样  -我开玩笑的 我喜欢...
- Mom. Come on.  - Joking. I like...
-我挺喜欢他的  -好
- I like him!  - OK.
我希望一切顺利
And I want to say I hope this can be nice.
我真的很欣慰你能过来
I really appreciate your coming over here.
好呢 不用担心
OK. It's no worries.
我的旅行代理专办这种负疚之旅
My travel agent specializes in guilt trips.
我来了
Hey! Hey!
不好意思 我来迟了吗
Apologies. Did I miss anything?
-没有  -祝你开心
- No.  - Happy day.
我是卡洛琳·科林伍德 很高兴见到你
Caroline Collingwood. Pleased to meet you.
我也是 阁下
Likewise, your excellency.
我是格雷戈里·赫施
Gregory Hirsch.
格雷格
Greg!
-你是蛋蛋格雷格  -什么
- You're Greg Egg.  - Excuse me?
你就是蛋蛋格雷格
You're Greg the Egg!
你出生的时候看起来就像一颗变形的蛋
When you were born you looked like a little misshapen egg.
我... 确实... 我听说过...
I... did... Yeah, I did hear tell of...
我的天 你爸爸以前
Oh, God. And your dad used
尝试睡遍全索萨里托[旧金山]的男人
to try and sleep with all the men in Sausalito.
你母亲怎么样
How's your mother?
挺好的 对 挺好
Uh, good. OK, yeah.
有偿付能力 目前看来 无债一身轻
Solvent, currently. Debt free.
好极了 进来吧
Great. Come on in.
来看看我们的小教堂
Come and see our little church.
这些是我所有声名狼藉的 圈养黑奴的祖辈们
These are all my disreputable slave-owning ancestors.
真好
Very nice.
-我的天呐 汤姆 你看到了吗  -什么 格雷格
- Oh, my God. Tom, did you see?  - What, Greg?
-我看到什么了  -那个布鲁克林的姑娘
- Did I see what?  - That's the girl from Brooklyn.
你单身派对上的那个
From your bachelor party.
那个给你口交 还让你吞下自个儿存货的女孩
Who sucked your dick and made you swallow your load.
格雷格 这话不适合在婚礼上说
Greg, that's not very wedding-y.
-但那就是她  -我知道
- But that's her.  - I know.
格雷格 她叫塔比莎 在和罗曼交往
Greg, her name is Tabitha, and she and Roman are dating.
没有任何问题 所以拜托
Which is cool. So please,
别跟个白痴乡巴佬一样
do not act like an unsophisticated rube.
-好吧 城会玩啊  -没错
- OK. Wow.  - Yeah.
他很喜欢她 这也没什么
He really liked her, and it's fine.
只是奇葩的城里玩法之一
It's just one of those weird urban things,
就像你去看单口秀
like when you go to see standup
而台上的喜剧人是你的牙医
and the comedian is your dentist.
-行吗 懂了吗  -懂了 懂了...
- OK? Yeah?  - Yeah, yeah...
-你来了  -你好
- Hey!  - Hey.
-好  -那个
- Hey!  - So,
-我们该走了  -对 咱们走吧
- we should, uh, get going. - Yeah, let's do it.
顺便一提 我是威拉 康纳的伴侣
I'm Willa, by the way. I'm Connor's partner.
好极了
Fantastic.
你是做什么的 威拉
And what do you do, Willa?
我是个剧作家
Oh, um, I'm a playwright.
-真好  -是啊
- Wow. Fantastic.  - Yeah.
-谢谢你  -美利坚万岁
- Thank you.  - America.
你是做什么的 康纳
And what do you do, Connor?
我...
Well, um...
康纳其实什么都不做...
Connor doesn't really do anything.
对吗 老康
Do you, Con?
他们现在应该都聚齐了 帕特里克
I think they're all gathered now, Patrick.
-我们也去吧  -怎么了
- Shall we?  - What?
怎么了
What?
操
Shit.
我们就开门见山吧
Just to get things straight,
我猜令尊... 我理解令尊...
am I right that the father... I understand the father...
不能被打扰
Couldn't be bothered.
他身体不适... 不太舒服
He's... He's not well. He's not well.
是的 正是如此
Yeah, that's the story.
大家都记住这个说法
Everyone remember the story.
那么 我会来代替父亲的角色
So, uh, I will be performing the father role.
好极了
Great.
听着 我不是说你无所事事 只是...
Listen, I didn't mean you don't do anything. Just...
真可惜 因为你就是这么说的
Well, that's a shame, because that's what you said.
不 你懂的 我是说 你做的事不像我写作那样...
No, you know, I mean, nothing like my writing. Nothing kinda...
保护三万英亩的旷野 这也算无所事事吗
Safeguarding 30,000 acres of wilderness, that's nothing?
即将开启一档关于拿破仑历史的播客节目
Being on the verge of setting up a podcast on Napoleonic history
还吸引着可观数目的投资 这也算无所事事吗
with a considerable level of investment interest, that's nothing?
-不 当然不 只是...  -寻找着幸福的真谛
- No, sure, it's...  - Crackin' the nut of happiness
就像当代梭罗一样 这也算无所事事
like a modern day Thoreau, well, that's nothing.
老康 你很棒
Con. You're great, OK?
真的 我...
You are. I...
说了些蠢话
It was a dumb thing to say.
我们到了
Well, here we are.
卡洛琳没继承到的故居
The ancestral home Caroline didn't inherit.
她的眼中钉 肉中刺
The thorn in her side, the fishbone in her throat.
小时候 她连看都不让我们看
When we were kids, she wouldn't even let us look at it.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
这规模可真大
I mean, it's massive!
我讨厌这里
I hate it.
-听着  -怎么
- Hey, so, listen.  - Mm-hmm?
你知道那些加拿大人 是吧
You know the Canadians, right?
伊夫他们吗
Yves, et cetera?
就是退休基金的那些人
The pension fund guys?
-是  -知道
- Yeah.  - Yeah.
他们怎么看待我的
What do they think of me?
你指的是什么 在哪种语境
How do you mean? What's the context?
我没法给你个语境
I can't give you context.
好的 这语境就有意思了
OK. That's very interesting context.
-听着 作为朋友...  -怎么
- Look, as a pal...  - Uh-huh?
假如说 有个私募股权
Say there was a situation where private equity
正尝试收购一个主流媒体
was trying to buy out a major media company
并设一个新的总裁
and install a new CEO.
-他们会怎么看我  -你认真的吗
- How would they view me?  - Are you serious?
操 那又怎样 他们是共同投资者吗
Fuck. So what, they're co-investors?
得了吧 你知道这些人的
Come on, you know those guys.
他们私底下觉得
Behind closed doors, are they of the opinion
我能上任
I'm the real deal,
还是仍待历练
or in training?
在这种情况下 一个老朋友还有机会
And would there be room to wet the beak of an old pal
-分杯羹吗  -弗兰克 此话甚早
- in such a situation?  - Frank, too soon. Too soon.
别对着我的利益瞎激动
Get your hard-on out of my soup.
好吧
Ok.
-所以呢  -这个嘛...
- So? - Well...
我觉得他们对你很有耐心
I think they have a lot of time for you,
但可能也有些问题
but there may be certain questions.
-见鬼  -你懂的
- Oh, shit.  - Well, you know,
他们觉得自己才是个中强手
they think they're hot shots.
他们还说一些难听的笑话
They make hard jokes.
例如
As in?
就有时你不在
Well, sometimes when you were absent
他们曾说你是"乌贼阴茎环"
they used to refer to you as "The calamari cock ring."
我都不懂是啥意思
I don't even know what that means.
我觉得意思是 他们觉得我像个
I think it means they think of me as a cock ring
乌贼肉做的阴茎环 弗兰克
made from calamari, Frank,
不言自明好吗
it's pretty self-explanatory.
-我们找的什么说法  -我觉得
- So what do we say?  - Well, I thought
我们准备说成是"患病"
we were gonna say "Illness."
不 我不喜欢这理由 显得很弱势
No, I don't like illness. Plays weak.
好吧 那说成是"繁忙"
OK, we can say "Busy."
哪个混蛋会繁忙到连亲女儿的婚礼都不去的
What prick's too busy to attend his own daughter's wedding?
那就"家庭不和"
OK, "Family rift."
然后我们介绍背景说 吉尔的竞选组织就像个邪教
But we background brief that Gil's campaign is like a cult.
"这哀伤的参议员对西沃恩·罗伊作了什么法"
"What is this grieving senator's mysterious hold on Shiv Roy?"
我们就这么透点消息出去
We sprinkle some of that.
这弄得她很弱势 也搞得我像是个...
It makes her look weak. And it makes me look like I'm...
我的孩子们都没发疯 或是自杀
None of my kids have gone round the bend, or offed themselves.
我们总是宣传 你是个好父亲
We've always pushed that you're a good dad.
-为什么  -因为你就是个好父亲
- Because? - Because you are a good dad.
那么 如果你不想说是
So, if you don't want to say, I mean,
公务繁忙或患病...
work or illness or...
又或者家庭不和 那我们该...
rift, do we just...
他妈的 没法自圆其说了
Fuck it. There's no way out.
我觉得 如果你真想去...
I mean, if you want to go...
我不想去
I don't want to go.
但就是他妈的没办法了
But there's no other fucking way out.
我们可以满足你的任何要求
We can do whatever you want us to do,
如果你认为我们做错了 那我很抱歉
and I'm so sorry if you think we've done the wrong thing,
但他们打来告诉我说 他在来的路上
but they literally just called and told us he was coming.
-谁要来  -老爸 还有玛西娅
- Who's coming?  - Dad. And Marcia.
-等等... 爸要来... 这里吗  -是的
- Wait... Dad's coming... here?  - Yeah.
我以为你不想他来
I thought you didn't want him to.
我是不想
I don't.
这可是你的婚礼 所以...
I mean, it's your wedding, so...
是的 所以我不想让他来
Yeah. I don't want him here.
他从没道过歉
He's never apologized.
但玛西娅打给了汤姆 然后...
But Marcia called Tom, and...
很显然我还得去问小西
And obviously I had to ask Shiv.
与此同时 她已经联系了夏洛特
Meanwhile, she's already called Charlotte,
-然后他们已经在路上了  -爸爸要来吗
- and they're on their way.  - Dad's coming?
是卫星发射的事吗 他在担心吗
Is it about the launch? Is he concerned?
是的 我敢肯定他整天都在想这事
Yeah, I'm sure he's thinking about that 24/7.
所以 你打算怎么做
So, I mean, what are you gonna do?
-你可以拒绝他  -是的 我本可以
- You could just say no.  - Yeah. I could.
但该怎么做 让保安他妈的把他拦住是吗
But what, just get security to fucking stop him?
-等等  -我真能这么做
- Hold on.  - I could do that.
你可以 但这气氛会变得很怪
Yeah you could, but it might cause a funny atmosphere,
因为他给这一切买了单 他花了钱
because he did pay for all this. He's paying.
如果他非要进来 我们该怎么办
If he's got the stones to walk in here, what are we gonna do?
放狗咬他 还是和他说这没位了 自个站着吧
Put the dogs on him? Tell him there's no seat, he's gotta stand?
他让我们别无选择
He's given us no choice.
我听说他要来
So now I hear he is coming.
-是的  -那可太好了
- Yeah.  - Well, that's wonderful.
-得了吧 妈  -没事 没关系
- Oh, come on, Mom.  - No, no. It's fine.
我只是希望你别忘了我
I just hope you won't forget about me
当你爸和
when your father arrives
他中东业务负责人到的时候
with the head of his Middle Eastern operations.
-玛西娅吗  -对 就是她
- Marcia? - Yeah, Marcia.
你还觉得她有点... 那个吗
Do you still find her a bit...? You know.
其实我们在老爸生病期间处得不错
Actually, we became quite close during Dad's illness.
好吧
Oh, well.
那画面肯定很甜蜜
What a sweet little scene that must have been.
一定感人极了
Very touching, I'm sure.
-其实这也挺好的  -为什么
- Actually, it's quite good.  - Why?
你变成自己婚礼上第二重要的人了
Just you're being the second-most important person at your wedding.
能缓解点压力
Take the pressure off.
这酒真香
Mm. Oh, this is delicious.
我很高兴你喜欢它
Well, I'm very glad you like it.
因为它很贵好吧
Because it cost a pretty penny.
真的很香 值这个价
Well, it's delicious. It tastes like it.
-抱歉 就一小会  -没关系
- Um, sorry. Just a second? - Oh, no. Of course.
-你好  -你好
- Hi.  - Hi there.
有什么"蛋白质食品"供我们吃吗
Got any protein for us to use?
蛋白质 我他妈的又不是给你下蛋的母鸡
Protein? I'm not a fuckin' hen to lay you eggs.
-我是政治战略家  -我知道 只是... 吉尔
- I'm a strategist.  - I know. It's just... Gil.
-干嘛  -他有话跟你说
- What?  - He'd like a word.
好的
Ok.
-你好  -你好啊
- Hey. Hey! - Hey. How ya doin'?
我必须得说 你们选的酒简直棒极了
I gotta say, you knocked it out of the park with the wine.
香飘万里
It's delicious.
吉尔
Gil.
听着 我不想小题大作
Listen, I don't mean to be overly dramatic,
但我同意来前你一再保证
but I was assured when I accepted
你父亲不会到场
that your father wouldn't be here.
我知道 计划有变 我也猝不及防
I know. Plans changed, I was ambushed.
我觉得这可不行 西沃恩
This is not OK from my POV, Siobhan.
这牵累到我了
This compromises me.
你当时也强烈希望吉尔过来
And you were very eager that Gil would come along.
这就有点...
I mean, that's...
是的 我当初邀请你时
Well, yeah, when I invited you
也没想到要干这么无聊的工作
I didn't realize it was gonna be a chore.
他就是太沉重了 小西
He's just weighty, Shiv.
自带重力场
He carries his gravity.
他不是人 是他妈个星球
He's not a man, he's a fucking planet.
这里没有记者 也没人拍照
Look, there's no press, and there's no pictures.
有干扰器和一只老鹰来击落无人机
We got jammers and a fucking hawk to take out drones.
就像什么都没发生过
It'll be like it never happened.
我听说你或许有我能用上的
I hear you might have something explosive
爆炸性新闻
I can use.
可能吧 我在努力
Yeah, maybe. I'm working on it.
但现在还不行
But just not yet.
我们一起打垮泛美吧 小西
Let's destroy ATN, Shiv.
这难道不是送给美国人民的
Wouldn't that be a nice wedding gift
超棒的结婚礼物吗
to the American people?
当然
Oh, yeah, sure,
我只是担心它也会伤害旁系亲属
I'm just concerned about collateral damage.
-汤姆  -汤姆吗
- Tom. - Tom?
-他会没事的  -其实
- He'll be fine. - Says the man
你肯定连自己在说什么都不知道
who has literally no idea what he's even talking about.
小西 得了
Shiv, come on.
我有各种说辞来抨击垄断 媒体
I have all the arguments on monopolies, and news,
和公共领域的腐败
and the coarsening of the public sphere,
但我现在听自己说话
but I kind of start falling asleep
都有点快睡着了
when I hear myself talk.
给我点猛料 小西 来根炸药
Give me something salty, Shiv. Get me a stick of dynamite
我就能炸爆他的肥屁股
I can shove up his fuckin' ass!
行 我知道了
OK, I get that.
过来 你认得吉尔
Come here. You know Gil.
当然
Yeah, sure.
很高兴见到您 伊维斯参议员
Pleased to meet you, Senator Eavis.
我也是
Likewise.
走出邪恶帝国的感觉怎样啊
How are you finding it outside the evil empire?
我很好 谢谢你
Oh, fine. I'm fine, thank you.
您在这狮穴里感觉如何
And how do you like it here in the lion's den?
我以前去过动物园
Oh, I've been to zoos before.
您喜欢品我们的香槟吗
You like drinking our champagne?
我是"今朝有酒今朝醉"的那种人
I'm a "Champagne for all" Guy,
不是养生派
not a "Gruel for all" Guy.
你认得伊维斯参议员吧
Hey, you know Senator Eavis.
无产阶级的守卫
Sword of the dispossessed
以及陈年香槟爱好者
and lover of vintage champagne.
严格说来 我该揍你一顿
I guess technically, I should take a swing at you.
严格说来 我该叫你乱诽谤的人渣
Technically, I should call you libelous scum.
是你停止胡扯
Are you gonna calm the shit-talk down,
还是我们干脆撕破脸面
or are we gonna have to ramp things up?
你爸能别再
Is your dad gonna stop
毒害我们伟大共和国的政论了吗
poisoning the discourse of our great republic?
你有笔记本电脑吗
Have you got a laptop?
看到网络舆论了吗 我们现在是他妈的好人了
Do you see the shit out there? We're the fucking good guys now.
好好玩 放松点
Join in, by the way. Feel free.
不要吗
No?
小西 你的人在这污蔑我们公司
Shiv? I mean, your guy here is shit-talkin' our company.
我们不聊那个的
Oh, yeah, we don't talk about that.
会有利益冲突
That would be a conflict of interest.
谎言
Oh, lies!
因为你... 那些谎言
Oh, 'cause you... Yeah, the lies.
等不及听明天的大谎言了 对吧
Can't wait for the big one tomorrow. Right?
这双手可不会自个撸起来
Well, these hands aren't gonna fuck themselves.
很高兴见到你 瘪四参议员
Nice to meet you, Senator Beavis.
瘪四与大头蛋: 不宜儿童观赏的卡通影片 此处瘪四和伊维斯拼写相似
-恭喜  -谢谢
- Congratulations. - Thanks.
-很高兴终于见到你了  -我是汤姆·威姆士丹
- Nice to finally meet you. - Tom Wambsgans.
看得出来 我是纳特
Obviously. Nate.
好的 好
Uh-huh. Right.
是
Right.
我只是想谢谢你邀请我
I just wanted to say thanks for having me.
我是塔比莎
I'm Tabitha.
你好 我对你知之甚少
Hi. Well, I've heard very little about you.
我能说什么呢
What can I say?
强者胜出
Best man won.
什么胜出
As in?
你赢得了小西 哥们
You won the Shiv-off, pal.
运气不错
Good luck.
对 你... 你是谁来着
Right. And who... who are you again?
纳特·苏弗雷利
Nate? Sofrelli?
她难道从没... 好尴尬啊
Did she never... This is embarrassing.
-你是肯德尔的朋友吗  -对
- Are you a pal of Kendall's? - Yes.
对 对 对
OK. Ah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
小西和我 很久以前曾交往过...
And Shiv and I, uh, back in ancient history we...
我知道了 懂了
Oh, right. Oh! Oh, I see.
好吧 她可能说过
Oh, OK, maybe she did.
-对  -可能说过
- Right. - Maybe she did.
所以你说强者胜出
Ah. The best man won.
或许吧
Maybe.
有个舅舅最后
There was an uncle who
和猴子一起住在直布罗陀
ended up living in Gibraltar with a monkey,
他诈骗了我外曾祖父
and he swindled my mom's grandpa.
我们小时候经常会过来 她住在附近
We used to come here as kids. She lives nearby.
挺好 引以为戒啥的
Oh, very good. Keep the wound fresh and all that.
那啥 我得走了
You know what, I'm gonna split.
我看到我的准丈夫和我前任聊天
I can see my husband-to-be talking to my ex,
让我感觉有点抓狂
and it's making me feel like I want to hurl.
-很高兴见到你  -行吧 我也是
- So, great to meet you. - Yeah, fair. You too.
祝你今晚开心
Have a good night.
只想说句...
Just to say...
你父母真是太慷慨了 用这款美酒招待我们
so kind of your parents to have paid for all this delicious wine.
您太客气了
Oh, not at all, not at all.
他们想出份力 才...
They wanted to make a contribution, so...
他们昭告天下的技法也挺聪明的
So clever the way they're letting every single person know.
好吧...
Oh. Oh, good...
你还好吗
You OK?
还行 我刚才好像被你妈捅了一刀[毒舌]
Yeah, I think I just got stabbed by your mom,
但也不太确定
but I'm not completely sure.
一贯如此
Oh, yeah, that's how it works.
你会在一小时内流血而亡
You'll bleed out in about an hour.
我能和你说... 几句吗
Can I... Can I talk to you for... two seconds?
好
Uh, yeah.
我只是想在这
So I just wanted to get you up here
跟你谈谈座位安排
to talk about the table plans.
你有没有再考虑...
Oh. And have you thought any more about... Ow!
要不要告诉我那个秘密
whether you want to tell me about the secret thing?
我只想说...
And I just wanted to, uh, say...
我见到纳特了
that I, uh, I did meet Nate.
你...
Oh, you...
你以前就见过他 好像
You've met Nate before. I think.
没有吗
No? Oh.
好吧... 他是个...
Uh... Oh, well, he's a...
他是个好同事
you know, he's a good colleague,
是肯德尔的朋友
and, uh, he's a friend of Kendall's.
他们以前在上海共事
They ran around in Shanghai together.
他还是个自私鬼
And he's a dick.
人挺好 但是身上有
Well, he's OK, but he has
某种自私的特质
a certain dickish quality about him.
-这样  -我好像我以前...
- Uh-huh. - I think I've mentioned him...
和你提过他
to you before.
听着 小西...
Look, Shiv, uh...
这是真的吗
Is this real?
你什么... 什么意思
What do you... What do you mean?
我... 是不是个大笨蛋
Am I... Am I a total jerk?
你真的想这样做吗
Do you really want to do this?
因为我们不必如此
'Cause we don't have to.
这样做
Do this?
-宾客全都到齐了  -是
- All the people are here. - Yeah.
而且... 我想
And... besides, I want to.
我确实... 确实想这么做
I do...I do want to.
我说 这...
I mean, is this...
我们到什么阶段了
W-What level are we on?
你在背着我偷吃吗
Are you fucking around on me?
-汤姆  -说真的
- Tom. - Honestly?
这个纳特...
This Nate...
你知道 我能...
you know, I can...
我能... 能感觉出来
I can... There are vibes.
汤姆 是怎样 只要两个同事关系好...
Oh, Tom. What, as soon as two colleagues are close...
在华盛顿就会有绯闻
D.C. Loves gossip.
当然
No, sure.
有时会有流言蜚语
Sometimes there are rumors,
有些人 确实不会乱搞
and people, you know, they're not fucking.
但有时候他们的确在搞
But sometimes they totally are.
真的吗
Honestly?
这是真的
This is real.
我没有背着你偷吃
I'm not fucking around on you.
好吧 我相信你
Well, I trust you.
那就好
Good.
谢谢
Thank you.
这样... 我就安心了
And that put... puts my mind at rest.
所以...
So...
在...
You know, when...
我们刚见面时 我简直一团糟
when we met, I was in such a mess.
我需要你
I need you. Hmm?
我真的需要
I do.
我...
I...
如果你想知道一些机密
If you want to know about the secret stuff,
邮轮航线的机密 我会告诉你
the cruise line stuff, I'll tell you.
因为我们要相互信任
Because we have to be able to trust.
对吗
Right?
是吗
Yeah?
是的 那太棒了
Yeah, that'd be great.
-你还好吗  -好哇
- Hey. Hey. How ya doin'? - Hi.
-孩子们在哪儿  -他们在楼上
- Where are the kids? - They're upstairs.
-好的  -他们在睡觉
- Cool. - They're sleeping.
-好的  -我看到小西了
- Yeah. Right. - I saw Shiv.
新婚夫妇怎么样了 还好吗
How are the happy couple? OK?
你知道的 保持表面和气
Good, you know, maintaining the veneer.
你还好吗
Mm-hmm. You OK?
我好极了 今天早上
I'm fantastic. I did, like,
我大概做了一百二十个俯卧撑 所以 我觉得我还好
120 push-ups this morning, so, yeah, I think I'm OK.
你做了一百二十个俯卧撑
Wow. Wow. You did 120 push-ups.
拉瓦 我现在有很多事要做
Rava, I just have a lot goin' on right now.
这不是...
It's not...
你更放松的插曲之一吗
not one of your more relaxing interludes?
不 这不是
Yeah. It's not.
我他妈压力太大了 还能说什么
I'm, uh, I'm a big fuckin' stress knot. What can I tell you?
可能有个肿瘤在由内而外地蚕食我
I probably have a tumor eating me inside-out.
你想再喝一杯吗
You want another drink?
你的律师们对我有点冷漠
Your lawyers have gotten a little quiet on me,
所以我只想知道 如果那...
so I'm just wondering if that's...
我不清楚那个
Oh, yeah, I don't know about that.
你能给他们点暗示吗
Can you maybe give them a little nudge?
当然
Sure.
我会给他们暗示的
I'll give them a nudge.
肯 肯
Ken. Ken.
-我了解你...  -是吗
- I know you... - Oh, yeah, you do?
-是的 我了解你  -真的吗
- Yeah, I know you. - Really.
如果你想谈谈的话 我就在这儿
And if you want to talk, I am here.
好的
Yeah.
我很好
Well, I'm good.
其实吧
Yeah, you know what,
说老实话我的律师在拖延
the truth is my lawyers are stonewalling
因为你的律师想干翻我
because your lawyers are trying to fuck me over.
那么我们是不是该把事留给他们
So shall we just leave it to them,
然后咱俩就能继续调情
and then you and me can just flirt
你也可以装你那恶心的假笑
and you can do your whole la-dee-fuckin'-da smile
我们又可以变得亲密啥的
and we can just be all chummy and everything
就因为我喜欢这感觉吗
because I love all that shit?
如果你这么需要嗑药的话 赶紧吸他妈一条吧
Have a fuckin' line if you need one that badly.
好的 我会的 好吗
Yeah, I will, OK?
-去你妈的吧  -谢谢
- Fuck you. - Thanks.
一切都不是你想的那样 你知道吗
Everything isn't what you think. You know?
你看不穿我
You can't see inside me
就因为我告诉了你那偶然的...
just 'cause I've told you the occasional...
抱歉
Sorry.
好吧 好吧 好吧 这他妈发生了什么
Well, well, well. What the fuck's going on here?
这看起来真他妈舒服啊
This looks mighty fucking cozy.
你好 肯德尔
Um... hi. Hi, Kendall.
-你好  -我们只是在...
- Hi. - We were just...
好吧 我们只是在说
well, we were just saying
我认为我第一次来这儿
that I think that the first time I came here
那时候你们还是孩子...
was back when you guys were kids, like...
好像是1986年
maybe 1986, I think?
-对 对 对 是的  -还记得吗
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Right. - Remember that?
是的 棒极了
Right. Great.
很抱歉 我得...
Sorry. I'm sorry. I should, uh...
在附近转转
circulate.
-好的  -好吧
- OK. - All rightie.
-我们等会儿见  -好的
- We'll see ya later. - Yep.
好吧 我很乐意说 但是我们非得今晚就说吗
Well, I'm happy to tell, but do we have to do it tonight?
因为这关系到公司包庇犯罪
You know, 'cause it's about the corporate cover-up of crimes
和组织化的性虐待
and institutionalized sexual abuse.
我操了
Oh, fuck.
倒霉的是老爹 走运的是吉尔
Well... bad for Dad. Great for Gil.
这不像是婚礼该谈的事
It's not very "Wedding-y."
是啊 但...
Yeah, still...
好的 那么...
OK. So...
有封口费
there were payoffs,
有...
there was...
合法和半合法的恐吓...
legal and semi-illegal intimidation...
你个人有巧妙的说辞来推脱吗
And do you personally have plausible deniability?
我认为有的 是的
Yes, I think so. Yeah.
数据已经深度清理过了
Digital deep-clean,
我还用碎纸机销毁了书面材料
and I shredded the paper material.
-太棒了  -加一个外部团队
- Great. - An outside team.
至于内部 格雷格在名册上签了字
And inside, signed the paper out-- Greg.
-格雷格  -是的
- Greg. - Yeah.
我觉得家人会可靠点
Just thought family would be safest,
而且格雷格是可消耗的
and Greg's expendable. You know.
什么 你会消耗... 格雷格吗
What, you'd... kill Greg?
不会 但你懂的 他是家人 对吧
No. But you know, he's family, right?
-所以我们让他闭嘴了  -好吧 行
- So we shut him up. - Yeah, OK, right.
你拿这个要干什么
What are you gonna do with this?
因为如果我把细节都告诉你了
'Cause if I give you the details,
这可能会重伤我的 小西
it could really hurt me, Shiv.
你不会让我受伤的吧
You're not gonna let me get hurt?
不会
No.
我还需要细节
I'll need specifics.
好吧
Ok.
那么...
So...
那么
So.
让他离我远些
Keep him away from me.
如我所见... 你爸爸来了个精致的入场
Your father's making a subtle entrance... as I see.
别这样
Hey.
来吧 尝尝禁果
Come on. Forbidden fruit.
纳特
Nate.
鸡下蛋了吗
Has the chicken laid the egg?
没有 还没有 别高兴了
Uh, no. Not yet. No joy.
看看你
Look at you.
我只求你专注于我一人
I'm desperate to make you concentrate
那怕只是一刻钟都好
on nothing but me for just 15 minutes.
你以为我以前专注过你吗
You think I used to concentrate on you?
纳特
Nate.
那么 蛋蛋格雷格
So, Greg Egg.
你觉得能维持多久
How long do you give it?
恕我迟钝
I'm sorry?
这段婚姻 你觉得能维持多久
The marriage. How long do you give it?
有什么问题吗
Is there doubt afoot?
我的意思是 我觉得他俩情比金坚
I mean, I for one think they look solid as a rock.
看吧 我只是守旧的浪漫派
But there you go, I'm just an old romantic.
好的 好的
Yeah, yeah!
-我们到了  -谢谢你
- Here we are. - Thank you.
-你好  -好哇
- Hello. - Hey.
我感觉... 好多了
I'm feeling... much better.
他好了不少
He's much improved.
太棒了
Great.
但其实我们没邀请你
Though you weren't actually invited.
没准我能让他们给你煎个蛋卷再找个座
Maybe I can get them to make you an omelet and find you a chair.
我觉得一般来说出了钱的都该有座 不是吗
I think usually the ones who are paying get a chair, no?
没看出来你还有贡献呢 玛西娅
Oh. I didn't realize you'd contributed, Marcia.
我太失礼了 多谢
So rude of me. Thank you.
我们快他妈去房间吧 行吗
Let's get to the fuckin' room, shall we?
我们的大人物怎么样了
How is the big man? Well, well, well.
很高兴见到你 还好吗
It's good to see you. You good?
很好 一切都好 股东可以安心
All good. Everything is good, acquisition-wise.
我们要做的
All we have to do is shut
就是让那边那人他妈的闭嘴
down the voice of the fuckin' people over there.
他在那儿
Oh, there he is.
-先失陪了  -没问题
- Will you excuse me? - Absolutely.
肯德尔
Kendall.
你好 老爸
Hey, Dad.
怎么了 儿子
So, what about it, son?
你想跳出战壕玩场足球游戏吗
You want to jump out of the trenches and play a game of soccer?
要我给你带些玉米来帮你熬过冬天吗
Can I bring you some corn to get you through the winter?
你最近怎么样 有什么新动作
How ya doin'? What's the news?
一直在忙
Oh, keepin' busy.
你的简历需要介绍信吗
You need a reference for your résumé?
说说你比较守时
Relatively punctual.
但容易多次不服从命令
Prone to bouts of insubordination.
是啊 你知道的
Yeah, well, you know.
那...
So...
你还要在外面胡闹多久
how long are you gonna fuck about on the outside?
你是在招募我吗
Uh-huh. You recruiting?
新的"不断受挫部"主任之类的吗
What, new Head of Being Continually Thwarted?
一家网络电视给你管 怎么样
How would a TV network suit you? Huh?
等我落实了 就让你当老板之一
One of the big guys when I land it.
那样行吗
Could that work?
你感觉到身上的压力了是吗
You feelin' the heat on your own?
有点了 是吗
Yeah? A little?
你要我回来...
You want me back, like to...
好把这件事写进新闻稿里吗
Like to put that in a press release?
我只是个和蔼的人
I'm just a lovely guy.
请帮我倒满 好吗
Can you top me up, please?
杂种 你们都聊了些什么
So? What was all that about, cocksucker?
他只是在跟我说你做的事有多么轰动
Oh, he was just telling me what a sensational job you're doing.
你大爷的
Fuck you.
他提到发射那事了吗
Did he mention the launch?
他知道是我促成的吗
Does he know that I've accelerated?
我说什么好笑的话了吗
Say something fuckin' funny?
你好
Hello.
我是卡洛琳·科林伍德 新娘的母亲
Caroline Collingwood. Mother of the bride.
您好 我是斯图伊
Oh. Hi, I'm Stewy.
你觉得能维持多久
So, how long do you give it?
我想会是永远
Uh, I'd say forever.
或是直到小西离开一周 要看哪个先来了
Or until Shiv goes away for the week, whichever comes first.
失陪了
Excuse me.
你个... 禽兽
You... beast.
妈妈 我听说你一直在问
Hi. Mom. I hear you're asking
"你觉得能维持多久"
"How long you give it."
只是用来破冰的俏皮话
Just a cheeky icebreaker.
好吧 但真是太他妈可怕了
OK, well, it's pretty fuckin' horrible.
不是针对你 小西
It's not all about you, Shiv.
其他人需要有话说
Other people need something to say.
好的 那你能问他们
OK, well, can you ask
鱼的价格而不是这个行吗
them about the price of fucking fish instead?
我喜欢你的女朋友 小罗
I like your girlfriend, Ro.
谢谢 我在一个色情派对上认识的她
Oh, thank you. I met her at a sex party
那时候她在给新郎口交
where she was giving the groom a blowjob.
-你该和她结婚  -什么
- You should marry that one. - Excuse me?
小西 别把一切看得这么严肃
And Shiv, stop taking everything so seriously.
我是想添砖加瓦
I'm trying to sparkle.
当别人问我这段婚姻能维持多久 我说的是永远
When people ask me how long I give it, I say forever.
-好吧...  -会是永远的
- OK, well... - It will be forever.
-好的 谢谢  -或者感觉像是永远
- Well, thank you. - Or it'll feel like forever.
她说自己想当个老顽童
She says she's being impish.
她就是个冷酷的婊子
She's being a stone cold bitch.
今晚晚些时候你想碰个头吗 我们一起
Hey, you want to meet up later tonight? All together?
-老地方吗  -是的
- At the place? - Yeah.
那么...
So, uh...
...你跟白鲸谈过了吗
...you talked to the white whale?
他有什么要说的
What'd he have to say?
没什么 我的意思是
Nothing. I mean,
他只是在支撑自己的位置
he's just shoring up his position.
这不是真的 他承受着压力
It's not real. He's under pressure.
你好吗 没有犹豫吧 你还好吗
Are you good? No wobbles, right? You OK?
我应该不会被伏击吧
I'm not gonna get coldcocked here, am I?
因为我听弗兰克说
'Cause I heard from Frank
加拿大人好像不怎么喜欢我
the Canadians might not be too keen on me.
你他娘的跟老爷钟说话了吗
You talked to the fucking grandfather clock?
他察觉什么了没
Has he signed anything?
没有 这样说太失礼了
No, that would just be rude.
他 他 他...
I mean, he-- he-- he--
他以前经常开他的赛斯纳飞机
he used to give me flying lessons
给我上飞行课
in his fuckin' Cessna.
拜托 兄弟
Come on, man.
你不再是一个小王子了
You're not a little prince anymore.
请你不要信赖"慢彻斯特的话多先生"
Don't rely on Sir Talky of Fuckchester, please.
没事的 斯图伊
He's good, Stewy.
我们要专攻北部 还是...
Are we working upstate, or...
您就是痴线先生吧
Ah. Mr. Fuckhead, I presume.
洛根·罗伊 洛根·罗伊 洛根·罗伊
Logan Roy, Logan Roy, Logan Roy.
我们可以对话吗
Are we allowed to talk?
罗伊先生 我个人对你只有钦佩 别无他意
I've nothing but admiration for you personally, Mr. Roy.
真的吗
Oh, really?
这就是该说的场面话 不是吗
It's the sort of thing you say, isn't it?
真高级
Ooh. Classy.
那么 你手里有什么东西来对付我
So, what is it you've got against me?
是你把局面变成人身攻击
You're the one making it personal.
我只是想做好本职工作
I'm just trying to do my job,
考虑到每个人 而不仅仅是我自己
think of everyone, not just myself.
受益个人就是受益所有人
The interest of each is the good of all.
这就是全部法律
That is the whole of the law.
你不必提醒我亚当·斯密的理论
You don't need to remind me of my Adam Smith.
-我教经济  -在哪教 幼儿园吗
- I taught economics. - Where? Kindergarten?
那么"各尽所能
What about "From each according to his ability,
按劳分配" 怎么样
to each according to his need"?
那么 这话不是我说的啊
What about, and this isn't me talking,
但是"他娘的超能先生"
but what about me, Mr. Fucking Ability,
我在自个汽车商店里拼了命地工作
busting my chops in my auto shop
难道是为方便一些体制内的穷酸鬼
so that some needy fuck from the projects
占我的时间手淫吗
can jack off on my time?
恐怕这就是问题所在
That's the issue, I'm afraid.
我倒觉得这只是人之本性的简化展现
Well, I find that a very reductive view of human nature.
我不创造本性
I didn't make human nature,
但我知道他们读了什么 看了什么
but I do know what they read and what they watch.
我深知人们真正想要什么
I make my nut off what people really want.
别跟我谈人
Don't tell me about people.
如果我不懂人 一周之内就会倾家荡产
I'd go flat broke in a week if I didn't.
很高兴见到你 参议员
Nice to meet you, Senator.
是啊
Yeah.
睡个好觉 爸
Sleep well, Dad.
-晚安  -谢谢
- Night. - Thank you.
可能是你十多年内最后一个好觉
Might be your last good one for a decade or so.
邮轮事件
The cruise situation.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talkin' about.
对 当然
Yeah, sure.
你可能很快就会知道了
Well, you might soon.
除非...
Unless...
你可以表现得更讨人喜欢一点 西沃恩
You could afford to be un petit peu plus agréable, Siobhan.
你不明白 玛西娅
You don't understand, Marcia.
我知道一个被宠坏的荡妇是什么样子
Well, I know when I see a spoiled slut.
你说什么
Excuse me?
你听到我说的了
Tu m'entends.
什么玩意儿 你算老几
What the fuck? Who are you?
除了是积攒力量的机器之外
Apart from a machine for gathering power?
你不知道人类能有多脆弱
You don't know how vulnerable a human being can be.
拜托
Oh, for fuck's sake.
你他妈是不是随心所欲地嗑药啊
Have you ever had a fucking grapefruit without an agenda?
他给你造了一个操场
He made you a playground,
你却以为是整个世界
and you think it's a whole world.
去你妈的
Well, va te faire foutre.
去外面的世界看看你能不能受得了
Go out and see how you like it.
给我滚
Fuck off.
你俩似乎比闺蜜都亲呢
Well, you two seem to be the best of friends.
别调侃了
Don't.
没事的
Aw, come on. It's OK.
宝贝
Hey. Pinky.
有人会联系你的
Someone will be in touch.
行
Great.
你太他妈棒了
You know, you're fuckin' great.
谢谢你
Thank you!
你不是祸水
You're not a head fuck.
不贱也不贪财[水蛭]
Or a bitch or a leech.
你嘴真甜
You say such pretty things.
你从来没提过留下过夜...
You never once asked to stay over...
不问我跟我爸关系如何 也不问信托
or how it works with my dad, or the trust,
也不问我的股份
or what my stake is, you know?
我只是单纯不感兴趣
I'm just pathologically incurious.
要是我准备好要娶你了呢
What if I was prepared to marry you?
什么
What?
小西快结婚了
Shiv's getting married,
肯德尔结过了...
Kendall got married...
所以你就想从奥林匹斯山上下来
I see. So, how about you come down off of Mt. Olympus
向一个凡人求婚
and propose to a mere mortal?
万一呢
Yeah, what if?
-不行  -不行吗
- No. - No?
-疯了  -哪里疯了
- Crazy. - Why is this crazy?
因为这不是一段正常的恋爱关系
Because this isn't a normal relationship.
为什么
Why?
一方面
Well, um, for one thing,
我们没做过
we never fuck.
做过啊
Oh, yeah, we do.
-不 没有  -得了吧
- No, we don't. - Yeah, come on,
当然做过 我们只是太忙了而已
yeah, we do, we've been busy, that's all.
你也就在我身边打了次飞机
No, you, like, kind of jerked off near me, once.
别恶心人
There's no need to be disgusting.
老实讲 罗曼 我跟新郎的性接触
To be honest, Roman, I've had more sexual contact
比跟你一起的还要多
with the groom than I have with you.
我让你别提这件事了
I asked you not to talk about that.
我跟很多男人睡过 罗曼·罗伊
I've slept with a lot of guys, Roman Roy,
你要是不乐意就尽早说
and if that is gonna be a problem, you better say.
对汤姆来说是麻烦 对我不是
It's not gonna be a problem, it's Tom's.
你到底想不想结婚
You want to get married or not?
宝贝
Babe.
你觉得这样就能让别人留下来吗
Do you think this is the way to get someone to stay?
格丽
Hey-hey, Gerri.
谢谢你来这儿见我
Thank you for meeting me here.
什么事
Uh-huh. What is this?
闲聊而已
Uh, just a chat.
没错 这是你的婚礼
Right. It's your wedding;
为什么我有种自己要悲剧[被干]的感觉
why do I feel like I'm about to get fucked?
晚了 是这样
OK, it's late. Here's the situation.
我知道邮轮部门那些见不得人的事情
I know all about the cruise division horror show.
和你们欲盖弥彰的事
And the cover-up.
吉尔正急着跟你当面对质
And Gil wants to go to town on you,
但我能拖他一会儿
but maybe I can get him to hold off
只要泛美别再播他老婆的
if ATN stops the personal stuff.
私事
Gil's wife.
你要让我们不喷他
You want us to stop attacking him?
可怜又脆弱的总统候选人
Poor liddle fwagile pwesidential candidate.
不是 初选的时候尽管攻击他
No, keep attacking him all through the primaries,
给我们炒话题 大选的时候
fire up our base, and then just back off
偃旗息鼓
for the general.
他们是记者 小西 不是遥控...
They're journalists, Shiv, not remote-controlled little...
他们当然是 所以我很确定
Yeah, sure they are. I just feel confident that, you know,
一两条我爸的公开评论 外加一封邮件
a little public comment or two from my dad, an email,
这些奴才就会改变想法了
and the minions realign pretty quick.
你是在...
So you are, um...
话讲清楚...
just to be clear...
不 我就是在恐吓你
Oh, yeah. No, I'm bullying you.
在勒索你
Yes. I'm blackmailing you.
我在用毁掉我爸来威胁你
I'm threatening to destroy my father,
-不管你怎么说  -你这么做很开心
- however you want to put it. - And you're happy with that?
拜托 事已至此
Oh, come on, it is what it is.
你以前可是个乖乖女
You used to be such a nice girl.
别把汤姆扯进来
And Tom needs to be clean.
让他置身事外 或者加官晋爵... 甚至送出国都行
Move him on, move him up... maybe abroad.
必须无迹可寻
Clean hands.
你很强势 小姐
You're very pushy, missy.
谢谢你 仙女教母
Thank you, fairy godmother.
要是上面同意我接受条件
And if I was authorized to accept,
你能让史密斯先生滚回华盛顿
can you get Mr. Smith to fuck off back to Washington
史密斯先生到华盛顿: 1939年喜剧电影 讲述热血青年史密斯为自由与民主决心向腐败宣战
别让他再脱裤子秀道德下限了好吗
and not pull down his pants to show off his amazing morals?
我应该能说服他做个肮脏的林登·贝恩斯·约翰逊[美国总统]
Yeah, I'm pretty sure I can persuade him that a dirty LBJ
比干净的麦戈文[同期美国政治家]好处来得多
gets more done than a clean McGovern.
好吧 晚安
OK, well, good night.
我亲爱的教母不给点婚姻上的建议吗
No marriage advice from my dear old godmother?
不知道 反正我也不太懂那些
I don't know. I was never very good at all that.
我丈夫去世了
My husband died.
别让老公死了
Don't let him die?
干嘛 我正跟人家谈到一半
OK, what is this? I was in the middle of a conversation.
老兄 我太对不起你了 杰西 能回避下吗
Dude, I am super-sorry. Jess, could you give us a second?
别 斯图 你认真的
No. Stew? Seriously.
肯 这里... 桑迪在线上
Ken, I got... I got Sandy on the line.
桑迪
Sandy?
-干  -怎么回事
- Fuck. - What is it?
他会跟你说的
He can tell you.
你来说 斯图 又整什么幺蛾子了
You can say, Stew. What's with the theatrics?
你能稍等下弗尼斯先生吗
Can you hold for Mr. Furness?
他刚还在的 人去哪儿了
He was just there. Where'd he go?
你不说吗 讲真的
You're not gonna say? Seriously?
这是伏击吗
Is this the coldcock?
我觉得最好让他来告诉你
I think it's just best that he tell you. That's all.
你真没种
You're such a pussy.
是... 是... 是加拿大那事儿吗
Is... Is it... Is this, uh, Canadian shit?
是关于熊抱信的事
Um... it's about that bear hug letter.
-讲启动并购那封  -行
- Starting the takeover? - OK.
加快节奏
An acceleration.
不 不 不 别闹
No, no, no. No, no, no. Fuck off.
这周末
This weekend.
-喂 桑迪  -在我妹妹的婚礼上
- Hello, Sandy? - At my sister's wedding?
你疯了吗 这是闹哪出
Are you insane? What do you want this to be,
一个婚礼和四个葬礼吗
One Wedding and Four Fuckin' Funerals?
注: 源于爱情电影四个婚礼和一个葬礼
喂
Hello?
喂 他都跟我说了
Hi. Yeah, he told me already.
绝对不行 没门 操
No, absolutely not, no way, no. No! Fuck this!
可你告诉弗兰克·弗农了
Listen, but you told Frank Vernon.
那是... 我... 我暗示他了
That has... I... I hinted.
有个记者联系上我们
We've been contacted by a reporter,
他们知道有人在密谋
and they know something's cooking.
我们明天就要开始否则就可能泄密
We have to go tomorrow or risk a leak,
那就死定了
which kills us.
不... 我们在一条船上
No. N... We're all together, OK?
现在... 现在时机不成熟
This is... This is not a good time.
现在就是个好时机
Well, it really is a good time.
你爸身处英国 不在现场
Your dad's out of the loop in the UK,
我们趁他不备
we catch him off-guard.
不
No.
我... 我需要 准...
I... I need to, uh, you know, pr...
准备下
p-p-p-prepare.
我...
Uh, I... I...
桑迪 我需要...
Sandy, I need...
时间准备
prep time.
好吗 为了和他们接触
OK? F-For the approach.
做鸡蛋饼免不了敲碎几个蛋
You can't make an omelet without breaking some dicks.
我很抱歉 好吗
Look, I'm sorry. OK?
我们信里保持联系
We'll be in touch with the letter,
然后到时候保持密切合作
and let's close-coordinate on the minute it's presented.
行吗 谢了 孩子
OK? Thanks, kid.
畜生
Motherfucker.
你怎么样
How ya doin'?
老康去哪儿了
Where's Con?
有...
Did...?
-老康 有人请他来吗  -你跟他说了吗
- Con? Was he invited? - Did you tell him?
别这样 搞什么
Come on. What?
想让我去叫他吗 我告诉威拉了
You want me to get him? I told Willa.
我的...
Uh... my...
他奶奶的
Fucking hell!
你们干嘛坐在船里
Why did you get in the boat?
不用 我就算了 我还有事呢
No, I'm good. I got shit to do.
啥玩意 那咱来这干吗
What?! Why are we here?
我还以为这是为了怀念从前
I thought this was for old times.
不要吗
No?
那你呢 你想抽一口吗
What about you, you wanna smoke my jay?
不了 我也有事呢
No, I got shit to do too.
好多事要处理
A lot cookin'.
去你的 什么鬼
What the fuck! Really?
行吧 就一口
All right, one hit.
这就对了 老铁
There we go, motherfucker.
又来
Diss.
- 截胡啊  -从前的日子嘛
- Intercepted. - Old times.
伙计们 听我说...
So listen, guys, um...
我有很重要的事要告诉你们
I do have something I need to tell you.
我之前去了老妈那里
Um... I was at Mom's earlier,
她要我帮她收拾那些文件什么的
she had me going through her papers and stuff,
整理好多东西
sortin' through some shit,
结果发现 小西...
and it turns out, uh, Shiv...
你是收养的
you're adopted.
还有 肯 你也是收养的
And Ken? You're adopted.
康纳 很明显他是收养的
And Connor is obviously adopted.
所以那些破玩意儿都是我的了
And so all that shit's comin' to me,
你们赶紧滚吧
so you can fuck off.
真对不起 我不知道为什么叫你过来
I'm sorry, I don't know why I asked you down here.
不用 没事儿
No, it's good.
恭喜了
Congratulations.
我替你高兴
I'm happy for you.
也替你高兴
谢谢
Thanks.
置身事外 看着我大显身手
It's gotta not be so easy for you
对你来说应该不容易吧
to be on the outside, seeing me do big shit.
对啊
Yeah.
你真慷慨 谢了啊
Big of you. Thank you.
对 好吧...
Yeah, well...
能拥抱一下吗
uh... can I suggest a hug?
-你讲真吗  -什么啊
- You serious? - What is it-- What?
-我是认真的  -干嘛啊
- Yeah. I'm serious. - Why?
你就... 快点 快过来
Just... come on. Bring it in.
-你们也想要的  -我要坐你身上
- You know you want to. - I'm goin' butt-first.
来咯
Here I come.
来啦
Here we all are!
我好像把他乳头揪掉了
I think I cut the nipple right off!
我不知道 我是说
I don't know, I mean, like,
我觉得我亏欠了他
I think I owe it to him,
但我不想由我来说这事
but I don't want to be the one to tell him.
你明白吗
You know?
我是说 如果他发现我知道了呢
I mean, like, what if he finds out that I knew?
要么...
Like... I either--
要么我亲口告诉他 然后亏欠了他
I either owe it to tell him-- owe it to him to tell him,
要么我绝口不提 但也算亏欠他
or I don't owe it to him to totally t-- not tell him.
你告诉他吧
I think tell him.
对 对 说得对
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
要不还是别说
Maybe don't?
我他妈真不知道
I don't fuckin' know.
行吧
Right.
不行 我们不能那样 因为这会曝光
Well, no we can't do that because that'll trigger
引起连锁反应...
the disclosure...
-我靠 是他  -等下 快停 停
- Oh, shit. That's him. - Wait. Stop. Stop.
今晚很愉快 谢谢你送我
Great night. Th-Thanks for the ride.
-汤姆  -喂
- Hey, Tom! - Hey, hey!
-等我一下  -早啊 格雷格
- Hey, wait up! - Morning, Greg!
听着 汤姆
Look, Tom, uh,
我... 我不知道...
I... I, uh, didn't know...
...到底应该怎么和你说
...like, exactly how to tell you this,
我真的整晚都在想应该怎么...
and I've been up all night trying to think exactly how to...
开这个口
broach--
所以我只想说 就是...
So I want to just say that-- that...
我觉得小西 她...
I think that Shiv is, like...
不是
No. N--
我觉得她外边有人了
I think she's having an affair.
没有 你弄错了
No. You're wrong.
不 不 我是说 不是...
No-- No, I'm-- I mean, not...
别说了 格雷格 闭嘴
Shut up, Greg. Shut up.
不是的 因为我...
Well, no, because I s-- I--
-你错了 错的离谱  -没准儿是我错了
- You are. You're wrong. - Maybe I'm wrong.
你弄错了 我们俩没事儿
You are wrong, so we're all good.
-好 那就好  -说完了 行了
- OK. G-Good. - OK? So, good.
谢谢你抽时间
Thank you for your time.
没事 你不想听下...
Yeah. And you don't want to hear...
我什么都不想听
I don't want to hear anything,
格雷格 因为这是个误会 行了吗
Greg, because it was a misunderstanding, OK?
-我很确定我看见的...  -快闭嘴
- I saw what I saw... - Shut up.
我说了闭嘴 安静
I just said shut up. Shut the fuck up.
好吧 但我觉得你应该知道...
All right, but I think you should know...
不 闭上你的嘴 格雷格
No. Shut-- Shut the fuck up, Greg.
-我是想帮你  -闭嘴 行吗
- I'm trying to help you. - Shut up, will ya?
-给我住口  -老兄 你干什么
- Fuckin' shut up. - Dude! What the hell?!
我说了你给我住口
I told you to fuckin' shut up!
你快松手
Get off of me!
-给我闭嘴  -你干什么你
- Just shut up! - What the fuck, man?!
-我就是  -住口
- Yeah, I-- - Shut up!
你知道
You know,
她提这个的时候我气坏了
I was quite outraged when she suggested this.
我不喜欢在美国以外待太久
I don't like being outside the U.S. For too long.
肯定不舒服
Doesn't sit well.
我还怀念本土的凉薄氛围
And there's a mercilessness I miss.
我受不了这些肮脏的买卖
I'm not used to these squalid little deals.
是啊 带枪不上保险栓
Yeah, living with the safety catch off,
做爱也不用套子
fuckin' without a rubber.
身边的人都是怂包
Everywhere else feels so soft.
你瞧这破地儿
I mean, look at this fuckin' place.
好吧 这里很有诗意
Yeah, well, it-- it's all quite refined.
什么诗意
Refined? Ahh.
奴隶 棉花和糖
Slaves. Cotton and sugar.
这个国家也就是离岸一个把罪恶
This country's nothing but an off-shore laundry
兑换成硬通货[白银]的洗衣房
for turning evil into hard currency.
你这是在告诉我 你在给共党工作吗
Is this where you tell me you're working for the communists?
现在这里都是谎话
And now it just lies here,
靠资本维生 吸移民者的血汗
living off its capital, sucking in immigrants
防止再长褥疮
to turn it and stop it getting bed sores.
我期待着看你玩崩盘
I was looking forward to taking you down.
你女儿非常能说服人
You've got a very persuasive daughter.
但还是交易更有说服力吧
But doesn't a deal feel so much better?
握个手吧
Handshake?
咱俩都不想弄脏自己的手 对吧
I don't think either of us want to get dirty, do we?
是啊
Yeah.
想开玩吗
You want to game it?
当然
Sure.
寄出那封信
Deliver the letter,
他召开董事会紧急会议...
he calls emergency board...
我们公开 然后舆论哗然
we go public, world blows up.
会计审查介入
The arbs dive in,
他对外开始编童话故事
he tells the world some fairy tales,
提出毒丸计划 还有其他措施
talks poison pill, other defenses,
毒丸计划: 以大量低价增发新股 来抵抗恶意收购
董事会提出"等等 我们不想被起诉"
board says, "Hang on, we don't want to get sued."
谢谢
Thank you.
爸说"去他的股东"
Dad says, "Fuck the shareholders,"
他联系分析师和对冲基金的人
he calls analysts, calls hedge funds,
试着用白衣骑士策略解决
tries to find a white knight,
为阻碍恶意接管的发生 寻找一家"友好"公司进行合并
打给我们 让我们玩蛋去
calls us, tells us to fuck off.
他是个好人 宝贝
He's a good man, Pinky.
他是个好人
He's a good man.
股价激增 因为大家都知道我们会赢
Price rockets, because everyone knows we're gonna win.
你觉得他有可能接受协议吗
You think there's a chance he'll just do a deal?
你没见过我爸吗
Have you met my dad?
没可能 他绝不退缩
Nope. He'll never retreat.
他只会反对 反对 再反对
It'll be hostile, hostile, hostile.
THE SUB-MAN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠